[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Come on.
Hang in there. Wan will be here soon.
Swamp Eel.
If I die,
please take care of Chia-yun and her mom.
Take care, my ass.
Take care of them yourself. Do you understand?
Fuck, who am I?
Swamp Eel. I rise to power by shooting flies.
You will be fine with me here.
Don't worry.
Hang in there. It'll be fine.
Hang in there, you hear me?
Stop! Over there!
-Fuck. -Go down here.
They're coming.
Swamp Eel, go. Wan and the others aren't coming.
Don't worry, they will come.
They will come.
You're lying to yourself.
If they were coming,
they would be here already.
Got it?
Hang in there.
Don't worry.
You will be fine with me here.
Hang in there. It'll be fine.
Hang in there, you hear me?
Fucking hang in there!
Hang in there.
I finally have the chance…
to take the shot I didn't get to take before.
You still think about Chi?
As long as I'm still alive,
I will never let it go.
Lin Wan-li,
you weren't fit to be our boss.
Anyway, once I leave the mountain,
I will die at my own brother's hands.
I would rather die at yours.
Go on and shoot.
Bastard.
You told us to ambush those traitors.
You said you'd send more men. But then what?
Chi's death was all your fault!
They were prepared
and had powerful backers.
If I had sent men to rescue you,
it would have only led to more deaths.
If I could do it all over again,
I would still make the same decision.
Swamp Eel,
tell Wan that I'm going on ahead.
Tell him to take care.
Do you know?
Up until Chi died…
he still called you "boss."
Remember.
You owe your life
to him.
You are awake, so you'll be fine.
THE FIXERS
ONE SHORT
Sweetie, don't worry.
It's just my ear that got a little injured.
I'm fine.
Pin and Hsiu, those two idiots.
They've nearly split up San He.
After I take care of things, I'll come home.
Okay, that's all for now.
Hsiu, our men saw with their own eyes
that your men kidnapped my brother.
You got the ransom.
If anything happens to my brother,
I will make you pay.
It could have also been you.
What did you say?
Enough!
What's going on? Why are you all crowding? Step back!
Boss.
Is this a stare-down?
Back off!
Pin,
my brother, thank goodness that you sent men to look for me.
However,
the two guys who kidnapped me
had nothing to do with Hsiu.
What did I say before?
Harmony above all.
It was all a misunderstanding.
For my sake,
let it be.
We must look after each other at San He,
so outsiders can't take advantage of us.
Since everyone is here,
I'll take this opportunity
to make an announcement.
This younger brother of mine
has coveted my seat for a long time.
I've let down too many people who called me their boss over the years.
It's time to step down.
Are you sure
you want to hand the seat over to your brother?
Starting today, everything related to San He
will be handled by my brother, Lin Kuei-pin.
I am retiring.
You have to be ruthless when you make your move.
Show no mercy, even to your own family, when necessary.
Like this time,
you wanted to take me, your own brother, out.
In this regard,
you do a better job than I do.
San He
is in your hands now.
Hsiu has helped us handle the situation with Fixer Shadow.
For people like us,
taking the blame for others is no big deal.
You are a major client of Ching He.
If you spread the word,
people will believe it.
Who on earth dares target Ching He's men?
Hey, eat more swamp eel.
It helps replenish blood and build muscle. Good for recovery.
Holy shit.
Truth is stranger than fiction.
This is practically a mansion.
-Lucky. -Yeah?
Sit. Greet our guest.
Goddamn, is it also called Lucky?
Is that on purpose?
What do you think?
How are you?
Is the wound any better?
It won't kill me.
Let me tell you, you got real lucky you had me.
If anyone else had treated that wound, you would've been done for.
When I was young, I was shot three times.
Left shoulder, right abdomen, and left thigh.
Two words sum it up. Close call.
Aren't you gonna ask what happened next?
Aren't you alive now?
Why ask?
You're like a brick wall. I might as well talk to my buddy, Lucky.
Lucky, come here.
Holy cow.
He looks so familiar. Isn't he running for mayor?
He's been on the news a lot lately.
-Why are you in a photo together? -Why so many questions?
Wait.
You two look alike.
He's my older brother.
He's your older brother?
Holy shit.
Hey, why would someone like you work as a fixer?
Are you out of your mind?
Can't I do what makes me happy? Eat your noodles.
Got it.
Everyone has their own secrets.
But you look more like the older brother.
Why don't you tell me
why you spared Lin Wan-li that day?
BELOVED FATHER, CHEN LIANG-CHI
BELOVED MOTHER, WANG SHU-HUA
Dad. Mom.
I got into a US college.
I might not be able to visit as often in the future.
Chi, exceptional children come from humble origins too.
Look how amazing Chen Chia-yun is. She's going to study in the US.
Don't be sad that she is leaving.
Watch over her and make sure everything goes smoothly.
Better yet, she brings home a boyfriend from abroad.
Come on.
Mom, I'm doing great.
Tristan looks after me. Don't worry.
We still play tennis together often,
although he can't beat me.
Dad…
Dad has been rather busy lately.
So he can't visit you. Don't take it to heart.
If only you were still here.
DAD
From my great-grandfather, a legislator,
to my father,
they have dedicated their lives to serving the people.
It's now my turn to take up the baton.
I will carry their legacy forward and continue to serve the people.
I would like to give special thanks to my mother today.
She has always been the quiet strength of our family.
Without her, we wouldn't be where we are today.
So today is a date?
I need a favor.
Why should I help?
I saved your life.
I looked for Lin Wan-li
to ask about someone.
Is it related to that necklace?
Yes.
Why are you looking for them?
He is very important to me.
His name is Gerald Chen.
He used to be a fixer for Yeh Yueh Tong.
Over a year ago, he suddenly vanished.
Lin Wan-li said Gerald went to him.
Gerald did come to see me.
It was about Yuan Tao Group's founder,
Zoe.
But I refused him.
I didn't want anything to do with Yeh Yueh Tong.
We believe that…
Zoe, one of Yuan Tao's founders.
Our future goals are…
Over a year ago, she died in an accident in Vietnam.
Around the same time Gerald went missing.
If I can get into Yuan Tao,
maybe I can find him.
I just met with Zoe's sister here.
You posed as Zoe's friend?
A college classmate when she was abroad.
I came back hoping to catch up with her.
I had no idea she passed away.
What about her partner? Is he doing okay?
Her husband is gone.
My sister had a happy family.
I never expected…
Zoe's husband was a legislative aide.
Not long before her accident,
he committed suicide.
Does her sister know about Gerald?
But she did mention Yuan Tao's other founder,
William.
We believe the value of blockchain technology…
My sister and William had a falling out.
I don't want to go around suspecting people, but
I heard them fighting over the phone.
Zoe said William destroyed her years of hard work building the company.
So you suspect that he is connected to Zoe's death.
He must know about Zoe.
He might lead us to more clues about Gerald.
I need your help.
Why don't you ask Yeh Yueh Tong?
As the second son of the Hsueh family,
you should have an easier time
approaching the cofounder.
When did you find out?
Did you think you hid it well?
Lately, besides Fixer Lucky,
you seem to have made a new friend from Yeh Yueh Tong.
We're not close.
But she did help with Lin Wan-li's case.
I don't mean to pursue it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have waited until now.
Did you get the necklace back?
I did.
I heard you have been close with a fixer from Ching He.
I was just getting my stuff back.
I didn't tell her anything about Ching He.
It isn't a bad thing to have a friend from Yeh Yueh Tong.
Of all the fixers, I trust you the most.
There are some things you should know.
Back then, Fixer Lunar,
who is now Madam Fan of Yeh Yueh Tong,
and her father
broke Ching He's rules.
That's why all the branches
elected me as Fixer Celestial.
Of course, Madam Fan has been holding a grudge over this.
A word of warning.
Soon, it won't be peaceful at Ching He.
So I'm worried
that there's a lot of trouble coming.
Be more careful.
Don't get dragged into it.
If Yeh Yueh Tong does anything that harms Ching He,
I will tell you.
Yeh Yueh Tong wasn't hired by San He this time.
How did Madam Fan find out?
Yeh Yueh Tong wasn't involved.
Mina Shen wanted to ask Lin Wan-li about someone.
Who?
Gerald Chen, also from Yeh Yueh Tong.
Every time I see you, I think of Gerald.
If he hadn't gone missing,
you two would have been Yeh Yueh Tong's best fixers.
I want to find him more than you do.
Are you sure that it's Mina who wants to find Gerald
and not Yeh Yueh Tong?
I'm certain.
Madam Fan,
were we ever hired by Yuan Tao?
Yuan Tao never hired Yeh Yueh Tong.
Anything else?
No.
CHRONIC GI DISCOMFORT? BEWARE OF PARKINSON'S!
WESTERN MEDICINE: PARKINSON'S MAY START IN THE GUT
GOLDIE
When did you get another cell phone?
Who is this Goldie?
A customer.
A man or a woman?
A man.
Do you actually have a mistress?
What mistress?
This is a work cell phone.
Then who is this Goldie?
I'll tell you who she is later.
No, I mean, Goldie.
You're the one bringing up a mistress.
I won't let this go until you explain!
Felix, I'm not done talking!
STIR-FRIED SWAMP EEL, SWAMP EEL NOODLES
Can I ask you something?
You go first.
Okay, I…
Have you heard of something called "Parinsane's disease"?
Parkinson's.
-Yes, "Parsonkin's." -"Parkin."
Gosh. Anyway…
Anyway, the doctor… The doctor says I have that disease.
What's the matter with you? How come you don't respond to others?
And you're such a picky eater.
Just listen to the doctor and don't overthink it.
Aren't you afraid I'll burden you?
I noticed your hand tremors a while ago.
I know some top doctors who treat wealthy patients.
I'll introduce them to you.
I was wondering
if you want to find a new partner.
I can't.
No one else wants to be my partner.
Your turn. What were you going to ask?
Mina.
She's using Lin Wan-li's leads to look for someone.
I want you in.
Okay, no problem.
I haven't even said who it is.
Of course. Thank goodness we had her on Lin Wan-li's case, right?
Besides, she's my partner's crush.
How could I not help?
I know you've got feelings for her.
Hey, I know a specialist for this kind of thing.
A love fixer.
That's me.
Let me teach you a few tricks, eh?
Will we violate Ching He's rules if we take a side job?
Fixer Celestial did assign this case.
GERALD CHEN
You're looking for him too?
Someone asked me to find Gerald.
Who is the client?
I can't tell you.
But finding Gerald
is very important to Ching He
because this concerns our survival.
Besides, Gerald has something important that belongs to Ching He.
A fixer from Yeh Yueh Tong is crucial to the survival of Ching He?
Seriously?
The chairman didn't say much.
Are you going to tell Mina that Ching He is looking for Gerald too?
No, we can't tell outsiders.
Okay. Since it's assigned, there shouldn't be any big problem.
But before we begin,
I need a small favor from you.
I don't lend money.
Not lending money.
…a rare appearance by former Interior Minister Jerome Hsueh
and his two sons.
Besides his eldest son, Tristan Hsueh, who is running for mayor,
his younger son…
He's your boss?
Don't freak out. What is so surprising?
My boss likes to be called Goldie, right?
Hello, Mr. Goldie.
You're being too polite.
With Fee around, I feel safe.
We'll chat more later. I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Let's eat first. Come.
Come on.
Why didn't you say your boss is a big shot?
So what?
I didn't prepare much today.
It's fine. Goldie prefers simple meals.
It's just some simple lobster and fish.
Dig in.
Have some.
Mr. Goldie, thank you for believing in Felix.
You know, he is reentering the workforce during a midlife crisis.
Finding a job isn't easy.
What midlife crisis?
This is called getting back in the game.
You're one to talk.
Why didn't you tell me you sold off the gambling house?
Now you know, don't you?
Don't say that.
I'm so lucky to have a bodyguard like Fee,
who is having a midlife crisis and reentering the workforce.
You're too kind.
But why does Goldie need my dad's protection?
Don't let his refined appearance fool you.
These ultra-rich heirs have a habit of picking fights and making enemies.
That is when they need smart and capable people like us
to help smooth things out.
Got it?
Yes. That's right.
Oh gosh, what fell?
To rich heirs who go around making enemies.
How did the pot lid fall on its own?
How should I know?
-I didn't put it here. -She's nagging again.
-Did it grow legs? -Eat up.
I only carried the dishes. It was Dad.
What's going on?
Felix Chiang, the pot lid doesn't go here.
You told me to put it here.
No, I didn't.
Don't be so loud. My boss is here.
-Right. -Keep it together.
I've been holding myself back a lot today.
AUTHENTIC TIEN-BU-LA
Okay, here comes the tien-bu-la.
Yours without cilantro.
Thank you.
Hold on.
You said both Zoe and William are in charge of Yuan Tao.
ARCADE
Through William, we can…
Find out how Zoe's death is connected to Gerald.
That's easy.
Kidnap William and just fucking beat him until he talks.
That tactic might work on trash like Sheng.
But for someone of his status,
you don't know who is backing him.
We have to be careful not to alert him.
So tell me.
How will you make him talk?
To get people like him to talk, you need leverage that can ruin him.
Use that leverage to make him comply.
What leverage could you have against a crypto guy?
We found evidence of him committing fraud.
My wife fell for a bogus coin like this.
How did you get this information?
Of course we did some legwork.
-Should we have waited for you? -Did I ask you?
Just swing your club. Don't butt in.
What kind of legwork did you guys do?
Damn, it's so windy. How am I supposed to play?
Hello?
Louis Hsueh?
Sure, no problem.
Hey, is his brother coming?
Okay, bye.
Do you come here often?
I do. My office is just next door.
You mean Yuan Tao?
You remember?
It's in the first line of your bio.
Right.
Hey, tell me.
Why do you use a dating app?
I mean, you don't look like you need it.
Buy me another drink.
And I'll tell you.
Okay.
I… I'll go order.
I…
Hey, excuse me. Um…
Let me see. Um…
PLEASE SCAN YOUR FINGERPRINT
The Hsueh's low-key younger son sought me out.
I'm flattered.
-Let's tee off. We'll chat. -Sure.
What a coincidence.
I just ran into Tristan at the Chamber. We talked about you.
What did my brother say?
Plug in the flash drive. The hacking software will install itself.
You can grab files remotely from another computer.
Thanks.
Wait, aren't you buying me a meal?
Next time.
Next time again.
I'm just being used.
So he felt like you used him?
That's not fair.
Right?
And I didn't tell him to drive me every day.
I split the bills with him too.
Anyway, we kept fighting, so we're done.
Of course.
Sorry, I drank too much. I'm going to use the restroom.
Oh, okay.
Is this yours?
Oh, yes.
-Wait for me. -Okay.
You made that engineer wait until closing?
What else, then?
There's no information on Gerald in there.
Yuan Tao seems like a normal business.
But interestingly,
a year and a half ago, Yuan Tao transferred a large sum of money
to set up a new company called Tolita.
The person in charge is this financial influencer.
Hello, I'm Dolly. I'm happy to share…
San He used to do this too.
Gang leaders would hire front men to evade police scrutiny.
And I discovered
that Tolita was involved in fraud disputes.
Those affected were likely placated, so the news was suppressed.
This… This company, Tolita,
I don't think it's enough to ruin William.
That's why we keep digging. Why else are you here?
Stop asking and do something, will you?
Can you be more polite in front of a lady?
That's where Dolly Bit helps.
This is a brand-new opportunity
to buy a high-potential crypto coin at an extremely low price.
How come you want to invest in crypto?
With your family's resources, you can start an investment firm.
My brother likes politics.
I prefer making money.
Who would pass up money?
So we share an interest.
But I prefer it when everyone makes money.
Lately, I've been watching a crypto coin.
It's getting a lot of hype. It's called, um, Dolly Bit.
It's recommended by a YouTuber called Dolly.
Have you heard of it?
I have.
But that sort of obscure thing isn't right for you.
You're so against it.
You have some inside info?
Only inside info on Yuan Tao
that enables over 90% of my business partners to profit
through range trading.
Fuck.
The wind sure is strange today.
Members involved in the donation scandal will be thoroughly investigated,
no matter who they are or which party they belong to.
Sir, do you think someone is trying to manipulate public opinion?
I've initiated disciplinary action to expel him from the party tomorrow.
He's a legislator who has been supporting us.
If he finds out--
He won't find out.
To rise to the top, one has to be ruthless.
If I must be sacrificed one day,
then so be it.
Also,
I received a call.
William from Yuan Tao said your brother reached out to him.
He wants to invest in cryptocurrency.
What a small world.
Dad, what do you want me to do?
You both belong to the Hsueh family by blood.
But he must be useful to you too.
He will be helpful to us.
Dad, you can trust my judgment.
By the way,
what did the doctor say at the follow-up visit?
Let's focus on the fundraiser this week.
We'll talk about that next week.
Your work is our top priority.
TRISTAN HSUEH
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm testing how long I can hold a gun before my hand starts to shake.
Who doesn't shake when they hold their hand up?
That's true.
With Parkinson's, don't your hands shake when they're at rest?
The doctor said my case is special.
The most annoying part is that I don't know when it will start to worsen.
Using a gun is the last resort.
Whether you can hold one matters little.
What if my legs start getting stiff too?
I saw that your brother's political crisis was all over the news.
I don't need to worry about things in the family.
As fixers, we always solve problems for others.
But our own family problems are the hardest to fix.
We gotta approach this investment adviser, Hung Kuo-lung.
How is he related to Yuan Tao?
He isn't. He just runs stock scams.
We need you to play an easy mark to get concrete proof of William's fraud.
Can you play mah-jongg?
I'm super good at it.
What?
The membership is a non-refundable one-year contract.
I'll recommend another one tomorrow. That's all. Bye.
Hey, buddy.
If you have any sure bets, share them.
What do you do?
I haven't seen you here before.
I sell seafood. A small business.
So are you investing your profits to stay ahead of inflation?
Only cash makes me feel safe.
That's not okay.
Hey, young man, don't be like him.
With inflation, your money will lose half its value in ten years.
Who can you blame?
Folks, can we begin?
Right. I'm going first.
Here, Red Dragon.
My friend lost millions to an investment scam.
Millions! Who would dare invest after that?
-White Dragon. -White Dragon, kong.
Let me ask you. Do you stop eating if you get diarrhea?
You will eat food that doesn't give you diarrhea, right?
Whoever called you still thinks you scammed them, don't they?
Yes, lots of people get scammed out there.
There are many scammers too.
Just like the three of you.
You guys have been exchanging glances from the beginning.
If you want to hustle,
get some more practice.
Four Characters.
I know how to play the game.
Exposing you as hustlers
won't end well for me.
Here's what.
Finish this round nicely,
and let me win a little
so everyone wins.
We aren't hustlers.
We know all about you.
We need you, a hustler, to help us out.
You want my help?
Can you afford it?
Hold on.
I'm getting old. I can't beat you.
You couldn't beat me even when you were younger.
Haven't you been busy lately?
How come you're free for tennis?
Ever since Tomb-Sweeping Day, Dad's health has noticeably worsened.
I know you don't want to see him.
It's not me.
He doesn't want to see me.
He heard that you're investing.
He was quite happy.
Did William say that?
But my advice is,
if you're going to invest, there are better options.
What's wrong with William?
How do you know him?
There's nothing wrong with him. We just met at a cocktail party.
I feel like he's not very honest or smart.
Don't rush into investing with him.
Come on.
-You want to continue? -One last game.
CANNON
SOLDIER
Check.
That was a risky move.
You only have a chariot and a cannon left,
and you're rushing to give check?
HORSE
CHARIOT
Who says I was going for the general?
Once the surroundings are clear,
will capturing the general be an issue?
So are you here
to protect or sacrifice the general?
I can barely keep my elephant safe. How can I worry about anything else?
Recently, there was a big case.
My fixers screwed up.
I was told that I'm too old
and can't delegate properly.
They said if I'm too old, I should step down.
If they want you gone, they can find any excuse.
I still need the old elephant that you are.
CHARIOT
I'm just afraid that this elephant…
ELEPHANT
…will be taken out before it can protect you.
Madam Fan.
Keep an eye on Mina.
See what she has found so far.
Got it.
Target Zoe confirmed dead.
Subtitle translation by: